const floralQuiz = [
    {
        question: 'What flower is called the â€œqueen of the garden?',
        variants: [
            'Rose',
            'Peony',
            'Lily',
            'Tulip'
        ],
        answer: 'Rose'
    },
    {
        question: 'What flower is famous for always turning toward the sun?',
        variants: [
            'Sunflower',
            'Tulip',
            'Daisy',
            'Lavender'
        ],
        answer: 'Sunflower'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these flowers grows in water?',
        variants: [
            'Lily',
            'Lotus',
            'Orchid',
            'Aster'
        ],
        answer: 'Lotus'
    },
    {
        question: 'What do white roses symbolize?',
        variants: [
            'Passion',
            'Friendship',
            'Purity and innocence',
            'Forgiveness'
        ],
        answer: 'Purity and innocence'
    },
    {
        question: 'What flower in Japan symbolizes the brevity of life and the beauty of the moment?',
        variants: [
            'Sakura',
            'Chrysanthemum',
            'Lily',
            'Orchid'
        ],
        answer: 'Sakura'
    },
    {
        question: 'What does the yellow tulip mean?',
        variants: [
            'Happiness and sunshine',
            'Envy',
            'Love',
            'Farewell'
        ],
        answer: 'Happiness and sunshine'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which flower likes shade and humidity?',
        variants: [
            'Violet',
            'Rose',
            'Gladiolus',
            'Lavender'
        ],
        answer: 'Violet'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which flower should not be placed next to fruit because they hasten its wilting?',
        variants: [
            'Lily',
            'Tulip',
            'Narcissus',
            'Rose'
        ],
        answer: 'Narcissus'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these flowers can be rooted in water?',
        variants: [
            'Geranium',
            'Peony',
            'Sunflower',
            'Rose'
        ],
        answer: 'Geranium'
    },
    {
        question: 'What does the white lily mean in the language of flowers?',
        variants: [
            'Forgiveness',
            'Innocence and purity',
            'Secret love',
            'Strength'
        ],
        answer: 'Innocence and purity'
    }
];

export default floralQuiz;